Guide to the American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA) National Office Records WAG.281
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Administrative Files
  - Pension and Welfare Funds: Meetings, Board of Trustees, Reports and Related Material, Jan 1984 (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - Pension and Welfare Funds: Meetings, Board of Trustees, Correspondence, Financial Statements and Related Material, Apr 1984 (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - Pension and Welfare Funds: Meetings, AFTRA Fund Report, Bernstein-Macauly, Inc. Client Report, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Pension and Welfare Funds: Meetings, Presentation Outlines [Portfolio Review and Investment Presentation], 1984 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Pension and Welfare Funds: Memorandum and Reports, Apr 1991 - May 1991 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Pension and Welfare [Health and Retirement Funds]: Minutes, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Pension and Welfare Funds: National, Local Remittance Report Forms, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Pension and Welfare Funds: Newscasters, Audit, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Pension and Welfare Funds: Newscasters, Benefit Packages, New as of Aug. 17, 1987, 1986-1987 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Pension and Welfare Funds: Newscasters, Benefits Agreements, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Pension and Welfare Funds: Newscasters, Benefits, CBS, 1986 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Pension and Welfare Funds: Newscasters, Company Plans, ABC, 1985-1987 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Pension and Welfare Funds: Newscasters, Correspondence, Arbitration Against ABC, NBC, CBS, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Pension and Welfare Funds: Newscasters, Lists, 1979-1985 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Pension and Welfare Funds: Newscasters, Lists of Casters from ABC, CBS, NBC, undated (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Pension and Welfare Funds: Newscasters, Network Benefits, 1978-1984 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Pension and Welfare Funds: Newscasters, Notes, Lists, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Pension and Welfare Funds: News Department, Benefit Plans, undated; 1986 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Pension and Welfare Funds: Pension Fund Actuarial Valuation and Review, Dec 1988 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Pension and Welfare Funds: Remittance Report Forms, 1984-1985 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Pension and Welfare Funds: Report, Nelson, Frank, Jun 1989 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Pension and Welfare Funds: Reports, "Exhibit C" Benefit Eligibility, Summary of Financial Statements, undated (found in 1991 files) (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Pension and Welfare Funds: Reports, "Exhibit C", "Exhibit D", 1991 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Pension and Welfare [Health and Retirement Funds]: Retirement Plan, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Pension and Welfare Funds: SAG Pension Plan and Related Correspondence, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Pension and Welfare [Health and Retirement Funds]: Segal Advisors, Inc., 1989-1990 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Pension and Welfare (Segal Reports) (Committee), 1964-1973 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Pension and Welfare Funds: Weber, Lipshie & Co., 1986 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Per Capita, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Per Capita: Correspondence, Friedenreich, Dan, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - "Performance Rights in Sound Recordings" Volume II, International Report (Folder 1 of 4), 1977 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - "Performance Rights in Sound Recordings" Volume II, International Report (Folder 2 of 4), 1977 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - "Performance Rights in Sound Recordings" Volume II, International Report (Folder 3 of 4), 1977 (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - "Performance Rights in Sound Recordings" Volume II, International Report (Folder 4 of 4), 1977 (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - Performers with Disabilities: Conference (with Equity and SAG), 1989-1990 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Performing Arts Employment: General, 1977-1981 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Performing Arts Employment: "A Guide to Federal Funding Sources for the Performing Arts" [Other Materials Attached], 1977-1983 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Performing Arts Employment: Survey (folder 1 of 2), Dec 1977 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Performing Arts Employment: Survey (folder 2 of 2), Dec 1977 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Performing Arts Employment: Survey (revised version of 1977 survey), 1978 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Permissions: Armed Forces Radio and Television, 1960-1962 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Permissions: Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Permissions: Correspondence, 1971-1977 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Permissions: Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Permissions: Correspondence, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Permissions: Correspondence, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Permissions: Correspondence, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Permissions: Correspondence, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Permissions: Department of Defense, Correspondence, Armed Forces Television, 1955-1967 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Phono Code: Correspondence, 1986-1993 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Phono Code: Correspondence, Stroock and Lavan, 1991-1992 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Phono Code: FCC Rule Changes, undated (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Polen, Nat Scholarship Fund: Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Polen, Nat Scholarship Fund: Donations, 1981-1982 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - PBS: Made in America, Correspondence, Proposal, Related Material, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - PBS: Made in the USA, Budget, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Radio Register: Magazine, 1938-1939 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - "Radio Yesterday" (Booklet), undated (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Randolph, A. Philip Institute: "The Failure of Black Separatism" by Bayard Rustin, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Read Files/Blues, Oct 1972 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Read Files/Blues, Nov 1972 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Read Files/Blues, Dec 1972 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jan 1973 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Read Files/Blues, Feb 1973 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Read Files/Blues, Mar 1973 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Read Files/Blues, Apr 1-16, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - Read Files/Blues, Apr 17-30, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Read Files/Blues, May 1973 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jun 1973 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jul 1-16, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jul 17-31, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Read Files/Blues, Aug 1-17, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Read Files/Blues, Aug 20-31, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Read Files/Blues, Sep 1973 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Read Files/Blues, Oct 1973 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Read Files/Blues, Nov 1973 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Read Files/Blues, Dec 1973 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jan 1974 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Read Files/Blues, Feb 1974 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Read Files/Blues, Mar 1974 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Read Files/Blues, Apr 1974 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Read Files/Blues, May 1974 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jun 1974 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jul 1974 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Read Files/Blues, Aug 1974 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Read Files/Blues, Sep 1974 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Read Files/Blues, Oct 1974 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Read Files/Blues, Nov 1974 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Read Files/Blues, Dec 1974 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jan 1975 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Read Files/Blues, Feb 1975 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Read Files/Blues, Mar 1975 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Read Files/Blues, Apr 1975 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Read Files/Blues, May 1975 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jun 1975 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jul 1975 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Read Files/Blues, Aug 1975 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Read Files/Blues, Sep 2-30, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Read Files/Blues, Oct 1975 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Read Files/Blues, Nov 1975 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Read Files/Blues, Dec 1975 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jan 1976 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jan 1976 - Feb 1976 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Read Files/Blues, Mar 1-31, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Read Files/Blues, Apr 1-12, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Read Files/Blues, Apr 13-30, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Read Files/Blues, May 1976 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jun 1-18, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jun 20-30, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jul 2-20, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jul 23-30, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Read Files/Blues, Aug 5-31, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Read Files/Blues, Sep 7-15, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Read Files/Blues, Sep 16-30, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Read Files/Blues, Oct 1-22, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Read Files/Blues, Oct 25-31, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Read Files/Blues, Nov 1-17, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Read Files/Blues, Nov 18-30, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Read Files/Blues, Dec 1-15, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Read Files/Blues, Dec 16-31, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jan 1-14, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jan 17-28, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Read Files/Blues, Feb 1-8, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Read Files/Blues, Feb 9-28, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Read Files/Blues, Mar 1-15, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Read Files/Blues, Mar 15-31, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Read Files/Blues, Apr 1-25, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Read Files/Blues, Apr 26-28, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Read Files/Blues, May 1-13,1977 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Read Files/Blues, May 16-31, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jun 1977 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jul 1-20, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jul 21-31, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Read Files/Blues, Aug 1977 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Read Files/Blues, Sep 1-19, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Read Files/Blues, Sep 20-30, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Read Files/Blues, Oct 1-14, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Read Files/Blues, Oct 17-31, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Read Files/Blues, Nov 1-13, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Read Files/Blues, Nov 14, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Read Files/Blues, Nov 15-30, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Read Files/Blues, Dec 1-15, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Read Files/Blues, Dec 16-31, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jan 1-17, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jan 18-31, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Read Files/Blues, Feb 1-23, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Read Files/Blues, Feb 24-28, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Read Files/Blues, Mar 1-11, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Read Files/Blues, Mar 14-17, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Read Files/Blues, Mar 18-28, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Read Files/Blues, Mar 29-31, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Read Files/Blues, Apr 1-17, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Read Files/Blues, Apr 18-28, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Read Files/Blues, May 1-17,1978 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Read Files/Blues, May 18-31, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jun 1-18, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jun 19-30, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jul 1-21, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jul 24-31, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Read Files/Blues, Aug 1-15, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Read Files/Blues, Aug 15-31, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Read Files/Blues, Sep 1-20, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Read Files/Blues, Sep 20-29, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Read Files/Blues, Oct 1-19, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Read Files/Blues, Oct 20-31, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Read Files/Blues, Nov 1-17, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Read Files/Blues, Nov 20-30, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Read Files/Blues, Dec 1978 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jan 1-17, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jan 18-31, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Read Files/Blues, Feb 1979 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Read Files/Blues, Mar 1-15, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Read Files/Blues, Mar 16-30, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Read Files/Blues, Apr 1979 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Read Files/Blues, May 1-15, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Read Files/Blues, May 16-31, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jun 1-18, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jun 19-29, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jul 1979 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Read Files/Blues, Aug 1979 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Read Files/Blues, Sep 1-12, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Read Files/Blues, Sep 13-31, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Read Files/Blues, Oct 1979 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Read Files/Blues, Nov 1979 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Read Files/Blues, Dec 1-21, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Read Files/Blues, Dec 21-31, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jan 1980 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Read Files/Blues, Feb 1980 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Read Files/Blues, Mar 1980 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jul 1980 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Read Files/Blues, Aug 1980 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Read Files/Blues, Sep 1980 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Read Files/Blues, Oct 1980 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Read Files/Blues, Nov 1980 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Read Files/Blues, Dec 1980 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jan 1981 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Read Files/Blues, Feb 1981 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Read Files/Blues, Mar 1981 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Read Files/Blues, Apr 1981 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Read Files/Blues, May 1-13, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Read Files/Blues, May 14-27, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jun 1981 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jul 1981 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Read Files/Blues, Aug 1-19, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Read Files/Blues, Aug 20-30, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Read Files/Blues, Sep 1981 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Read Files/Blues, Oct 1981 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Read Files/Blues, Nov 1981 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Read Files/Blues, Dec 1981 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jan 1982 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Read Files/Blues, Feb 1982 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Read Files/Blues, Mar 1982 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Read Files/Blues, Apr 1982 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Read Files/Blues, May 1982 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jun 1982 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jul 1982 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Read Files/Blues, Aug 1982 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Read Files/Blues, Sep 1982 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Read Files/Blues, Oct 1982 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Read Files/Blues, Nov 1982 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Read Files/Blues, Dec 1982 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jan 1983 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Read Files/Blues, Feb 1983 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Read Files/Blues, Mar 1983 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Read Files/Blues, Apr 1983 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Read Files/Blues, May 1983 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jun 1983 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jul 1983 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Read Files/Blues, Aug 1983 (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - Read Files/Blues, Sep 1-15, 1983 (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - Read Files/Blues, Sep 16-30, 1983 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Read Files/Blues, Oct 1983 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Read Files/Blues, Nov 1983 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Read Files/Blues, Dec 1983 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jan 1-12, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jan 13-31, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Read Files/Blues, Feb 1984 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Read Files/Blues, Mar 1-16, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Read Files/Blues, Mar 20-30, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Read Files/Blues, Apr 1984 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Read Files/Blues, May 1984 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jun 1984 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jul 1984 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Read Files/Blues, Aug 1-16, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Read Files/Blues, Aug 17-30, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Read Files/Blues, Sep 1984 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Read Files/Blues, Oct 1-16, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Read Files/Blues, Oct 17-31, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Read Files/Blues, Nov 1984 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Read Files/Blues, Dec 1984 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jan 1985 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Read Files/Blues, Feb 1985 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - Read Files/Blues, Mar 1985 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - Read Files/Blues, Apr 1-16, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Read Files/Blues, Apr 17-30, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Read Files/Blues, May 1985 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jun 1-6, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jun 7-28, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jul 1985 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Read Files/Blues, Aug 1985 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Read Files/Blues, Sep 1985 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Read Files/Blues, Oct 1-9, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Read Files/Blues, Oct 10-31, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Read Files/Blues, Nov 1985 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Read Files/Blues, Dec 1985 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jan 1986 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Read Files/Blues, Feb 1-20, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Read Files/Blues, Feb 21-28, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Read Files/Blues, Mar 1-10, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Read Files/Blues, Mar 11-31, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Read Files/Blues, Apr 1-14, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Read Files/Blues, Apr 15-30, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Read Files/Blues, May 1986 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jun 1986 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jul 1986 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Read Files/Blues, Aug 1986 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Read Files/Blues, Sep 1986 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Read Files/Blues, Oct 1986 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Read Files/Blues, Nov 1986 (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - Read Files/Blues, Dec 1986 (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jan 1987 (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - Read Files/Blues, Feb 1987 (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - Read Files/Blues, Mar 1987 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Read Files/Blues, Apr 1-15, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Read Files/Blues, Apr 16-30, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Read Files/Blues, May 1-12, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Read Files/Blues, May 13-31, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jun 1987 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jul 1987 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Read Files/Blues, Aug 1-7, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Read Files/Blues, Aug 4-26, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Read Files/Blues, Sep 1987 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Read Files/Blues, Oct 1987 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Read Files/Blues, Nov 1987 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Read Files/Blues, Dec 1987 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jan 1988 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Read Files/Blues, Feb 1-17, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Read Files/Blues, Feb 18-29, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Read Files/Blues, Mar 1-21, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Read Files/Blues, Mar 22-31, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Read Files/Blues, Apr 1-13, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Read Files/Blues, Apr 14-30, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Read Files/Blues, May 1-17, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Read Files/Blues, May 18-31, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jun 1988 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jul 1988 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Read Files/Blues, Aug 1-23, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Read Files/Blues, Aug 24-31, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Read Files/Blues, Sep 1988 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Read Files/Blues, Oct 1988 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Read Files/Blues, Nov 1988 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Read Files/Blues, Dec 1988 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jan 1989 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Read Files/Blues, Feb 1-20, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Read Files/Blues, Feb 21-28, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Read Files/Blues, Mar 1989 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Read Files/Blues, Apr 1989 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Read Files/Blues, May 1-21, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Read Files/Blues, May 22-31, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jun 1-8, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jun 9-21, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jun 22-30, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jul 1989 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Read Files/Blues, Aug 1989 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Read Files/Blues, Sep 1989 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Read Files/Blues, Oct 1989 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Read Files/Blues, Nov 1989 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Read Files/Blues, Dec 1-14, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Read Files/Blues, Dec 15-31, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jan 1990 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Read Files/Blues, Feb 1990 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Read Files/Blues, Mar 1990 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Read Files/Blues, Apr 1-7, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Read Files/Blues, Apr 8-23, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Read Files/Blues, Apr 24-30, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Read Files/Blues, May 1-15, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Read Files/Blues, May 16-31, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jun 1-17, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jun 18-30, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jul 1-20, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Read Files/Blues, Jul 21-31, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Read Files/Blues, Aug 1990 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Read Files/Blues, Sep 1990 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Read Files/Blues, Oct 1990 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Read Files/Blues, Nov 1990 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Read Files/Blues, Dec 1990 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Recording Industry Association of America: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1973-1979 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Recording Industry Association of America: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1978-1991 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Reporters Committee for Freedom of the Press: Correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Report to the President, Cable Communications, 1974 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Rockefeller Bros. Fund: "Labor Relations in the Performing Arts", 1967-1968 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Rogers, Will Institute, Memorial Fund: Burke Rehabilitation Center Referrals, 1978-1981 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Rogers, Will Institute, Memorial Fund: Correspondence, Minutes, Budget, 1975-1980 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Rogers, Will Institute, Memorial Fund: Correspondence, Minutes, Budget, 1981-1985 (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Rogers, Will Institute, Memorial Fund: Correspondence, Minutes, Budget, 1986-1991 (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor Institute for Cancer Research, 1960-1963 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor Memorial Foundation, 1964 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - "Screen Actors Seek TV Justice", by Walter Pidgeon, 1952 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Singers' Caucus: News, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - SMA Life Assurance Company: Statements of Value, AFTRA National, Deferred Compensation, 1985-1986 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Society of Motion Picture and Television Engineers: Symposium on Automated Monitoring, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Standard Data Corporation, 1988-1990 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Standard Data Corporation: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1974-1978 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Standard Data Corporation: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Standard Data Corporation: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1980-1988 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Star Television Network: Correspondence, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Sterling Manhattan Cable TV, Inc.: Agreement, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Stroock & Stroock & Lavan: Correspondence, 1989-1992 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Subsidies (Paid Out Monthly), 1984-1985 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Talent and Residuals, Inc.: Correspondence, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - TAT Communications Company: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Theatre Authority: Actors' Work Program (AWP), 1984-1992 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Theatre Authority: Balance Sheets, 1975-1976 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Theatre Authority: Balance Sheets, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Theatre Authority: Balance Sheets, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - Theatre Authority: Balance Sheets, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - Theatre Authority: Balance Sheets, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - Theatre Authority: Balance Sheets, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - Theatre Authority: Balance Sheets, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - Theatre Authority: Balance Sheets, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - Theatre Authority: Balance Sheets, 1987 (Box 54, Folder 26)